Guide to the James Harvey Rogers Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Index to Selected Correspondents
  - Fry, Charles Luther (1894-)
    - 37 TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1928 October 24 (Box 5)
      - 1929 January 7 (Box 6)
      - 1929 August 2 (Box 6)
      - 1932 April 6 (Box 10)
      - 1932 October 20 (Box 11)
      - 1932 December 5 (Box 11)
      - 1933 June 27 (Box 12)
      - 1935 January 3 (Box 16)
      - 1935 January 21 (Box 16)
      - 1935 January 31 (Box 16)
      - 1935 February 5 (Box 16)
      - 1935 May 23 (Box 16)
      - 1935 September 25 (Box 17)
      - 1935 October 12 (Box 17)
      - 1935 October 17 (Box 17)
      - 1935 October 22 (Box 17)
      - 1935 October 25 (Box 17)
      - 1935 October 29 (Box 17)
      - 1935 November undated (Box 17)
      - 1935 November 30 (Box 17)
      - 1935 December 23 (Box 17)
    - 2 TL (copies) written by James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
      - 1934 March 5 (Box 13)
      - 1934 March 15 (Box 13)
  - Furniss, Edgar Stephenson (1890-)
    - 104 ALS, TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1921 February 22 (Box 1)
      - 1922 January 19 (Box 1)
      - 1922 March 2 (Box 1)
      - 1922 May 9 (Box 1)
      - 1922 June 10 (Box 1)
      - 1923 March 26 (Box 2)
      - 1923 May 31 (Box 2)
      - 1923 June 22 (Box 2)
      - 1923 September 11 (Box 2)
      - 1923 September 13 (Box 2)
      - 1923 September 24 (Box 2)
      - 1923 October 11 (Box 2)
      - 1923 December 2 (Box 2)
      - 1924 November 17 (Box 2)
      - 1925 January 5 (Box 3)
      - 1925 January 28 (Box 3)
      - 1925 February 6 (Box 3)
      - 1925 March 29 (Box 3)
      - 1925 September 30 (Box 3)
      - 1925 October 15 (Box 3)
      - 1925 October 27 (Box 3)
      - 1925 December 2 (Box 3)
      - 1926 January 26 (Box 3)
      - 1926 February 19 (Box 3)
      - 1926 February 21 (Box 3)
      - 1926 March 8 (Box 3)
      - 1926 March 11 (Box 3)
      - 1926 March 31 (Box 3)
      - 1926 April 1 (Box 3)
      - 1926 April 12 (Box 3)
      - 1926 April 14 (Box 3)
      - 1926 May 6 (Box 3)
      - 1926 May 13 (Box 3)
      - 1926 May 20 (Box 3)
      - 1926 July 27 (Box 3)
      - 1926 August 5 (Box 3)
      - 1927 January 18 (Box 4)
      - 1927 February 3 (Box 4)
      - 1927 February 8 (Box 4)
      - 1927 February 28 (Box 4)
      - 1927 April 5 (Box 4)
      - 1928 January 19 (Box 4)
      - 1928 February 28 (Box 5)
      - 1928 March 23 (Box 5)
      - 1928 May 2 (Box 5)
      - 1928 May 15 (Box 5)
      - 1928 December 14 (Box 6)
      - 1929 February 14 (Box 6)
      - 1929 March 4 (Box 6)
      - 1929 March 14 (Box 6)
      - 1929 October 7 (Box 6)
      - 1929 November 18 (Box 6)
      - 1929 December 12 (Box 6)
      - 1929 December 19 (Box 6)
      - 1930 January 11 (Box 7)
      - 1930 January 16 (Box 7)
      - 1930 January 22 (Box 7)
      - 1930 January 28 (2) (Box 7)
      - 1930 February 12 (Box 7)
      - 1930 February 13 (Box 7)
      - 1930 February 26 (Box 7)
      - 1930 March 20 (Box 7)
      - 1930 March 29 (Box 7)
      - 1930 May 7 (Box 7)
      - 1930 May 19 (Box 7)
      - 1930 July 2 (Box 7)
      - 1930 September 29 (Box 7)
      - 1931 March 30 (Box 8)
      - 1931 April 29 (Box 8)
      - 1931 May 1 (Box 8)
      - 1931 August 11 (Box 8)
      - 1931 December 17 (Box 9)
      - 1932 January 29 (Box 10)
      - 1932 April 5 (Box 10)
      - 1932 May 4 (Box 10)
      - 1933 July 23 (Box 12)
      - 1933 August 3 (Box 12)
      - 1933 December 11 (Box 13)
      - 1934 February 9 (Box 13)
      - 1935 April 13 (Box 16)
      - 1936 February 8 (Box 18)
      - 1936 March 5 (Box 18)
      - 1936 March 10 (Box 18)
      - 1936 October 21 (Box 19)
      - 1937 January 4 (Box 20)
      - 1937 February 1 (Box 20)
      - 1937 March 2 (Box 20)
      - 1937 April 1 (Box 20)
      - 1937 July 19 (2) (Box 21)
      - 1937 July 23 (Box 21)
      - 1937 August 7 (Box 21)
      - 1938 January 6 (Box 22)
      - 1938 February 9 (Box 22)
      - 1938 April 25 (Box 22)
      - 1938 May 19 (Box 22)
      - 1938 September 19 (Box 23)
      - 1938 September 24 (Box 23)
      - 1938 October 15 (Box 23)
      - 1939 January 4 (Box 23)
      - 1939 February 3 (Box 23)
      - 1939 May 30 (Box 24)
    - 33 TL copies and telegram written by James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1922 June 13 (Box 1)
      - 1924 November 12 (Box 2)
      - 1925 February 9 (Box 3)
      - 1926 April 16 (Box 3)
      - 1927 January 15 (Box 4)
      - 1927 February 16 (Box 4)
      - 1927 November 9 (Box 4)
      - 1927 December 27 (Box 4)
      - 1928 February 1 (Box 4)
      - 1928 February 23 (Box 5)
      - 1928 April 27 (Box 5)
      - 1928 June 6 (Box 5)
      - 1929 February 9 (Box 6)
      - 1929 March 4 (Box 6)
      - 1930 January 15 (2) (Box 7)
      - 1930 February 18 (Box 7)
      - 1930 February [24-26] (Box 7)
      - 1930 March 15 (Box 7)
      - 1930 May 14 (Box 7)
      - 1930 May 24 (Box 7)
      - 1931 April 29 (2) (Box 8)
      - 1932 March 26 (Box 10)
      - 1933 December 9 (Box 13)
      - 1934 November 26 (Box 15)
      - 1936 February 12 (Box 17)
      - 1936 June 20 (Box 19)
      - 1937 July 21 (Box 21)
      - 1937 July 27 (Box 21)
      - 1938 January 11 (Box 22)
      - 1939 February 22 (Box 24)
      - 1939 May 18 (Box 24)
  - Gallup, George Horace (1901-). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New York, 1938 December 22 (Box 23)
  - Gay, Edwin Francis (1867-1946). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Cambridge, Mass., 1929 March 22 (Box 6)
  - Gayer, Arthur David (1903-1951)
    - 39 ALS, TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1933 January 30 (Box 11)
      - 1933 February 14 (Box 11)
      - 1933 February 18 (3) (Box 11)
      - 1933 February 21 (Box 11)
      - 1933 March 28 (Box 11)
      - 1936 August 26 (Box 19)
      - 1936 September 26 (Box 19)
      - 1936 October 5 (Box 19)
      - 1936 October 16 (Box 19)
      - 1936 October 18 (Box 19)
      - 1936 November 2 (Box 19)
      - 1936 November 7 (Box 19)
      - 1936 November 18 (Box 19)
      - 1936 December 1 (Box 19)
      - 1936 December 7 (Box 20)
      - 1936 December [9] (Box 20)
      - 1936 December 9 (Box 20)
      - 1936 December 14 (Box 20)
      - 1936 December 16 (Box 20)
      - 1936 December 24 (2) (Box 20)
      - 1937 January 6 (Box 20)
      - 1937 January 12 (Box 20)
      - 1937 January [15] (Box 20)
      - 1937 January [15-19] (Box 20)
      - 1937 January 29 (Box 20)
      - 1937 March 15 (Box 20)
      - 1937 March 23 (Box 20)
      - 1937 March 29 (2) (Box 20)
      - 1937 April 8 (2) (Box 20)
      - 1937 April 19 (Box 20)
      - 1937 July 2 (Box 21)
      - 1937 July 12 (Box 21)
      - 1937 November 16 (Box 21)
      - 1938 August 19 (Box 22)
  - Givens, Meredith Bruner (1899-)
    - 16 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New York
      - 1931 November 5 (Box 9)
      - 1931 December 4 (Box 9)
      - 1931 December 23 (Box 9)
      - 1932 February 3 (Box 10)
      - 1932 February 17 (Box 10)
      - 1932 February 20 (Box 10)
      - 1932 February 25 (Box 10)
      - 1932 March 17 (Box 10)
      - 1932 March 30 (Box 10)
      - 1932 May 2 (Box 10)
      - 1932 May 9 (Box 10)
      - 1932 June 10 (Box 10)
      - 1932 June 21 (Box 10)
      - 1932 October 25 (Box 11)
      - 1932 November 4 (Box 11)
      - 1932 December 27 (Box 11)
  - Glass, Carter (1858-1946)
    - TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1935 May 27 (Box 16)
    - TL (copy) written by James Harvey Rogers, New Haven, 1935 May 28 (Box 16)
  - Goldenweiser, Emanuel Alexander (1883-1953)
    - 4 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
      - 1927 January 5 (Box 4)
      - 1927 April 14 (Box 4)
      - 1935 October 24 (Box 17)
      - 1935 December 2 (Box 17)
  - Goldsborough, Thomas Alan (1877-1951)
    - 3 telegrams to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
      - 1932 March 15 (Box 10)
      - 1932 March 22 (2) (Box 10)
    - 2 TL (copies) written by James Harvey Rogers, Columbia, Mo.
      - 1922 November 21 (Box 2)
      - 1923 March 31 (Box 2)
  - Green, William (1873-)
    - 3 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
      - 1931 December 29 (Box 9)
      - 1932 January 4 (Box 9)
      - 1933 May 10 (Box 12)
  - Haig, Robert Murray (1887-1953)
    - 20 TLS, TL (copies) and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1926 October 9 (Box 3)
      - 1926 October 21 (Box 3)
      - 1926 October 23 (Box 3)
      - 1926 November 29 (Box 3)
      - 1926 December 10 (Box 3)
      - 1926 December 16 (Box 3)
      - 1926 December 17 (Box 3)
      - 1927 January 6 (Box 4)
      - 1927 June 2 (Box 4)
      - 1927 June 7 (Box 4)
      - 1927 June 24 (Box 4)
      - 1927 August 25 (Box 4)
      - 1927 September 1 (Box 4)
      - 1927 October 18 (Box 4)
      - 1927 October 25 (2) (Box 4)
      - 1927 November 18 (Box 4)
      - 1927 December 12 (Box 4)
      - 1930 May 16 (Box 7)
      - 1930 December 22 (Box 8)
  - Hall, Ray Ovid (1891-1952)
    - 57 ALS, TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1928 May 18 (Box 5)
      - 1928 June 5 (Box 5)
      - 1928 August 10 (2) (Box 5)
      - 1928 October 18 (Box 5)
      - 1929 May 31 (Box 6)
      - 1930 June 2 (Box 7)
      - 1931 May 8 (Box 8)
      - 1931 August 22 (Box 8)
      - 1931 September 8 (Box 8)
      - 1931 September 17 (Box 9)
      - 1931 October 19 (Box 9)
      - 1931 November 1 (Box 9)
      - 1931 November 4 (Box 9)
      - 1931 December 7 (Box 9)
      - 1931 December 17 (Box 9)
      - 1931 December 30 (Box 9)
      - 1932 March 4 (Box 10)
      - 1932 April 13 (Box 10)
      - 1932 May 6 (Box 10)
      - 1932 August 31 (Box 11)
      - 1932 September 4 (Box 11)
      - 1932 September 13 (Box 11)
      - 1932 October undated (Box 11)
      - 1932 November 19 (Box 11)
      - 1932 December 5 (Box 11)
      - 1933 February 16 (Box 11)
      - 1933 March 8 (Box 11)
      - 1935 July 13 (Box 17)
      - 1936 April 10 (Box 18)
      - 1937 April 11 (Box 20)
      - 1937 December 12 (Box 21)
      - 1937 December 18 (Box 21)
      - 1938 January 8 (Box 22)
      - 1938 January 12 (Box 22)
      - 1938 January 14 (Box 22)
      - 1938 January 21 (Box 22)
      - 1938 January 31 (Box 22)
      - 1938 March 17 (Box 22)
      - 1938 March 21 (Box 22)
      - 1938 April 26 (Box 22)
      - 1938 May 27 (Box 22)
      - 1938 August 13 (Box 22)
      - 1938 September 14 (Box 23)
      - 1938 September 26 (Box 23)
      - 1938 October 4 (Box 23)
      - 1938 October 7 (Box 23)
      - 1938 October 18 (Box 23)
      - 1938 October 21 (Box 23)
      - 1938 October 24 (Box 23)
      - 1938 October 28 (Box 23)
      - 1938 November 4 (Box 23)
      - 1938 November 8 (Box 23)
      - 1938 November 17 (Box 23)
      - 1938 December 17 (Box 23)
      - 1938 December 27 (Box 23)
      - 1939 January 11 (Box 23)
  - Hansen, Alvin Harvey (1887-)
    - 5 ALS and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1934 March 1 (Box 13)
      - 1938 January 3 (Box 22)
      - 1938 January 31 (Box 22)
      - 1938 December 19 (Box 23)
      - 1939 January 13 (Box 23)
    - 3 TL (copies) written by James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1938 January 6 (Box 22)
      - 1938 January 19 (Box 22)
      - 1939 January 16 (Box 23)
  - Hayes, Carlton Joseph Huntley (1882-)
    - 11 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New York
      - 1926 December 14 (Box 3)
      - 1927 January 13 (Box 4)
      - 1927 January 26 (Box 4)
      - 1927 September 20 (Box 4)
      - 1927 November 13 (Box 4)
      - 1927 December 20 (Box 4)
      - 1928 February 2 (Box 4)
      - 1928 February 16 (Box 5)
      - 1928 March 14 (Box 5)
      - 1928 April 16 (Box 5)
      - 1928 May 31 (Box 5)
  - Hopkins, Harry Lloyd (1890-1946). TL (copy) written by James Harvey Rogers, no place, 1934 October 31 (Box 15)
  - House, Edward Mandell (1858-1938)
    - 3 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New York
      - 1934 October 8 (Box 15)
      - 1934 October 22 (Box 15)
      - 1934 October 25 (Box 15)
    - 2 TL (copies) written by James Harvey Rogers, New Haven
      - 1934 October 4 (Box 15)
      - 1934 October 5 (Box 15)
  - Hull, Cordell (1871-1955)
    - 4 TLS and telegrams to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
      - 1933 November 10 (Box 13)
      - 1935 October 2 (Box 17)
      - 1936 June 17 (Box 19)
      - 1936 August 8 (Box 19)
    - 9 TL (copies) written by James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1933 November 9 (Box 13)
      - 1934 March 23 (Box 14)
      - 1935 September 30 (Box 17)
      - 1936 June 5 (Box 19)
      - 1936 August 8 (Box 19)
      - 1936 August 12 (Box 19)
      - 1936 August 13 (Box 19)
      - 1936 September 25 (2) (Box 19)
  - Hunt, Edward Eyre (1885-1953)
    - 33 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New York
      - 1928 January 30 (Box 4)
      - 1928 February 1 (Box 4)
      - 1928 February 14 (Box 5)
      - 1928 February 27 (Box 5)
      - 1928 March 8 (Box 5)
      - 1928 April 4 (Box 5)
      - 1928 April 20 (Box 5)
      - 1928 April 21 (Box 5)
      - 1928 May 24 (Box 5)
      - 1928 June 7 (Box 5)
      - 1928 June 9 (Box 5)
      - 1928 June 14 (Box 5)
      - 1928 June 22 (Box 5)
      - 1928 July 30 (Box 5)
      - 1928 August 13 (Box 5)
      - 1928 August 20 (Box 5)
      - 1928 September 13 (Box 5)
      - 1928 September 27 (Box 5)
      - 1928 September 29 (Box 5)
      - 1928 October 2 (Box 5)
      - 1928 October 3 (Box 5)
      - 1928 October 15 (Box 5)
      - 1929 January 11 (Box 6)
      - 1929 February 6 (Box 6)
      - 1929 February 18 (Box 6)
      - 1929 February 27 (Box 6)
      - 1929 April 27 (Box 6)
      - 1929 November 19 (Box 6)
      - 1929 December 5 (Box 6)
      - 1930 January 3 (Box 6)
      - 1930 February 24 (Box 7)
      - 1930 March 31 (Box 7)
  - Jackson, Gardner
    - 6 ALS, TLS and telegrams to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
      - 1933 February 25 (Box 11)
      - 1933 May 18 (Box 12)
      - 1933 May 26 (Box 12)
      - 1933 May 31 (Box 12)
      - 1933 June 21 (Box 12)
      - 1933 September 25 (Box 12)
  - Johnson, Alvin Saunders (1874-1971)
    - 36 TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, New York
      - 1923 November 19 (Box 2)
      - 1923 December 24 (Box 2)
      - 1931 November 19 (Box 9)
      - 1931 December 1 (Box 9)
      - 1931 December 17 (Box 9)
      - 1932 January 26 (Box 10)
      - 1932 January 27 (Box 10)
      - 1932 January 29 (Box 10)
      - 1932 February 8 (Box 10)
      - 1932 April 2 (Box 10)
      - 1932 April 5 (Box 10)
      - 1932 April 11 (Box 10)
      - 1932 April 25 (Box 10)
      - 1932 May 5 (Box 10)
      - 1932 June 7 (Box 10)
      - 1933 March 8 (Box 11)
      - 1933 May 5 (Box 12)
      - 1933 June 9 (Box 12)
      - 1933 July 18 (Box 12)
      - 1933 August 22 (Box 12)
      - 1933 August 25 (Box 12)
      - 1933 August 31 (Box 12)
      - 1933 September 13 (Box 12)
      - 1933 September 28 (Box 12)
      - 1933 October 23 (Box 12)
      - 1934 August 27 (Box 15)
      - 1935 December 10 (Box 17)
      - 1935 December 20 (Box 17)
      - 1936 January 14 (Box 17)
      - 1936 March 1 (Box 18)
      - 1936 June 1 (Box 18)
      - 1936 June 16 (Box 19)
      - 1936 November 10 (Box 19)
      - 1936 December 14 (Box 20)
      - 1937 February 1 (Box 20)
      - 1937 March 29 (Box 20)
    - 28 TL copies and AL draft written by James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1917 [January-Jun] (Box 1)
      - 1923 October 22 (Box 2)
      - 1925 April 3 (Box 3)
      - 1931 November 25 (Box 9)
      - 1931 December 4 (Box 9)
      - 1931 December 9 (Box 9)
      - 1932 January 16 (Box 9)
      - 1932 February 3 (2) (Box 10)
      - 1932 February 5 (Box 10)
      - 1932 April 4 (Box 10)
      - 1932 April 20 (Box 10)
      - 1932 April 30 (Box 10)
      - 1932 May 10 (Box 10)
      - 1932 May 11 (Box 10)
      - 1933 March 6 (Box 11)
      - 1933 March 16 (Box 11)
      - 1933 May 15 (Box 12)
      - 1933 June 10 (Box 12)
      - 1933 June 13 (Box 12)
      - 1933 September 26 (Box 12)
      - 1935 March 20 (Box 16)
      - 1935 December 12 (Box 17)
      - 1936 January 7 (Box 17)
      - 1936 June 18 (Box 19)
      - 1936 November 27 (Box 19)
      - 1936 December 11 (Box 20)
      - 1937 March 24 (Box 20)
  - Johnson, Nelson Trusler (1887-1954)
    - 6 ALS and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1934 July 14 (Box 14)
      - 1934 August 6 (Box 15)
      - 1934 November 28 (Box 15)
      - 1939 February 10 (Box 24)
      - 1939 February 18 (Box 24)
      - 1939 March 7 (Box 24)
  - Jones, Grosvenor Monroe (1883-)
    - 9 TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1928 May 3 (Box 5)
      - 1929 January 29 (Box 6)
      - 1929 November 20 (Box 6)
      - 1931 June 19 (2) (Box 8)
      - 1933 September 22 (Box 12)
      - 1933 November 11 (Box 13)
      - 1935 July 30 (Box 17)
      - 1935 October 24 (Box 17)
  - Kemmerer, Edwin Walter (1875-1945)
    - 3 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Princeton, N.J.
      - 1928 October 12 (Box 5)
      - 1928 October 22 (Box 5)
      - 1928 December 4 (Box 5)
  - Kendrick, Myron Slade
    - 11 ALS and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Ithaca, N.Y.
      - 1924 October 7 (Box 2)
      - 1925 May 4 (Box 3)
      - 1925 November 10 (Box 3)
      - 1926 October 24 (Box 3)
      - 1927 February 23 (Box 4)
      - 1929 May 12 (Box 6)
      - 1929 May 30 (Box 6)
      - 1930 May 2 (Box 7)
      - 1930 June 2 (Box 7)
      - 1933 May 23 (Box 12)
      - 1938 November 14 (Box 23)
  - King, Willford Isbell (1880-1962)
    - 4 ALS and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1921 June 11 (Box 1)
      - 1922 April 25 (Box 1)
      - 1931 September 23 (Box 9)
      - 1931 November 23 (Box 9)
  - Klein, Julis (1886-). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1928 June 16 (Box 5)
  - Knight, Frank Hyneman (1885-)
    - 2 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Chicago
      - 1931 January 20 (Box 8)
      - 1933 April 19 (Box 11)
  - Landis, James McCauley (1899-)
    - 3 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
      - 1935 January 25 (Box 16)
      - 1936 January 11 (Box 17)
      - 1936 December 17 (Box 20)
    - 3 TL (copies) written by James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
      - 1936 January 13 (Box 17)
      - 1936 January 31 (Box 17)
      - 1936 December 10 (Box 20)
  - Laylin, John Gallup (1902-)
    - 14 ALS and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1934 April 7 (Box 14)
      - 1934 November 30 (Box 15)
      - 1935 July 24 (Box 17)
      - 1935 December 6 (Box 17)
      - 1935 December 11 (Box 17)
      - 1935 December 19 (Box 17)
      - 1936 February 11 (Box 18)
      - 1936 July 23 (Box 19)
      - 1936 October 8 (Box 19)
      - 1936 November 12 (Box 19)
      - 1937 January 26 (Box 20)
      - 1937 February 19 (Box 20)
      - 1937 June 21 (Box 21)
      - 1937 August 4 (Box 21)
  - Leavens, Dickson Hammond (1887-)
    - 52 ALS, TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1931 November 19 (Box 9)
      - 1934 June 6 (Box 14)
      - 1934 June 15 (Box 14)
      - 1934 June 16 (Box 14)
      - 1934 June 30 (Box 14)
      - 1934 June undated (Box 14)
      - 1934 July 1 (Box 14)
      - 1934 July 22 (Box 15)
      - 1934 August 24 (Box 15)
      - 1934 August 27 (Box 15)
      - 1934 August 30 (Box 15)
      - 1934 September 1 (Box 15)
      - 1934 September 5 (Box 15)
      - 1934 September 7 (Box 15)
      - 1934 September 13 (Box 15)
      - 1934 September 14 (Box 15)
      - 1934 September 24 (Box 15)
      - 1934 September 29 (Box 15)
      - 1934 October 1 (Box 15)
      - 1934 October 5 (Box 15)
      - 1934 October 10 (Box 15)
      - 1934 October 13 (Box 15)
      - 1934 October 16 (Box 15)
      - 1934 November 14 (Box 15)
      - 1934 December 7 (Box 15)
      - 1934 December 18 (Box 16)
      - 1934 December 27 (Box 16)
      - 1935 January 2 (Box 16)
      - 1935 January 5 (Box 16)
      - 1935 January 9 (Box 16)
      - 1937 May 21 (2) (Box 21)
      - 1937 June 1 (Box 21)
      - 1937 June 29 (Box 21)
      - 1937 July 1 (Box 21)
      - 1937 July 13 (2) (Box 21)
      - 1937 July 14 (Box 21)
      - 1937 July 21 (Box 21)
      - 1937 July 23 (Box 21)
      - 1937 August 2 (2) (Box 21)
      - 1937 August 30 (Box 21)
      - 1937 October 21 (Box 21)
      - 1937 December 8 (Box 21)
      - 1938 January 19 (Box 22)
      - 1938 May 12 (Box 22)
      - 1938 October 31 (2) (Box 23)
      - 1939 January 9 (Box 23)
      - 1939 January 17 (Box 23)
      - 1939 February 6 (Box 23)
  - Lee, Ivy Ledbetter (1877-1934)
    - 9 TLS and telegrams to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1931 June 12 (Box 8)
      - 1931 June 23 (Box 8)
      - 1931 July 1 (Box 8)
      - 1931 July 21 (Box 8)
      - 1931 October 6 (Box 9)
      - 1932 March 1 (Box 10)
      - 1932 March 17 (Box 10)
      - 1932 May 26 (Box 10)
      - 1933 December 7 (Box 13)
    - TL (copy) written by James Harvey Rogers, 1933 Dec 21, Washington, D.C. (Box 13)
  - Le Hand, Marguerite A. (1898-1944)
    - TLS to James Harvey Rogers, 1937 Nov 9, Washington, D.C. (Box 21)
    - 6 TL (copies) written by James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
      - 1933 July 19 (Box 12)
      - 1933 August 31 (Box 12)
      - 1933 December 9 (Box 13)
      - 1934 October 2 (Box 15)
      - 1934 [Dec] undated (Box 15)
      - 1935 October 23 (Box 17)
  - Lippman, Walter (1889-)
    - TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, New York
      - 1933 December 19 (Box 13)
      - 1934 February 2 (Box 13)
    - 2 TL (copy) and telegram written by James Harvey Rogers
      - 1934 February 2, Washington, D.C. (Box 13)
      - 1934 March 23, San Francisco, Calif. (Box 14)
  - Lowden, Frank Orren (1861-1943)
    - 4 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1931 November 18 (Box 9)
      - 1932 December 22 (Box 11)
      - 1933 January 12 (Box 11)
      - 1933 January 31 (Box 11)
    - 3 TL (copies) written by James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1931 November 25 (Box 9)
      - 1933 January 9 (Box 11)
      - 1933 January 17 (Box 11)
  - MacIver, Robert Morrison (1882-)
    - 9 TLS and telegrams to James Harvey Rogers, New York
      - 1933 January 18 (Box 11)
      - 1933 January 20 (Box 11)
      - 1933 January 21 (Box 11)
      - 1933 March 1 (Box 11)
      - 1933 March 6 (Box 11)
      - 1933 March 7 (Box 11)
      - 1933 October 21 (Box 12)
      - 1934 January 17 (Box 13)
      - 1934 September 21 (Box 15)
  - Meyer, Eugene (1875-1959)
    - 2 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New York
      - 1931 September 22 (Box 9)
      - 1933 March 4 (Box 11)
  - Millikan, Max Franklin (1913-)
    - 9 TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1935 July 25 (Box 17)
      - 1935 July 29 (Box 17)
      - 1935 August 21 (Box 17)
      - 1935 November 26 (Box 17)
      - 1936 January 13 (Box 17)
      - 1936 February 2 (Box 18)
      - 1936 April 21 (Box 18)
      - 1936 July 1 (Box 19)
      - 1939 April 20 (Box 19)
  - Mitchell, Wesley Clair (1874-1948)
    - 14 TLS and TL copy to James Harvey Rogers, New York
      - 1921 November 14 (Box 1)
      - 1924 May 5 (Box 2)
      - 1924 May 15 (Box 2)
      - 1926 October 20 (Box 3)
      - 1928 February 16 (Box 5)
      - 1928 March 24 (Box 5)
      - 1928 March 31 (Box 5)
      - 1928 November 19 (Box 5)
      - 1929 February 13 (Box 6)
      - 1929 March 11 (Box 6)
      - 1930 November 28 (Box 7)
      - 1931 January 27 (Box 8)
      - 1931 January 31 (Box 8)
      - 1931 April 9 (Box 8)
    - 21 TL (copies) and AL (draft) written by James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1919 April-1937 March 12 (Box 1–20)
  - Moley, Raymond (1886-)
    - 2 TL (copies) written by James Harvey Rogers, no place
      - 1933 April 23 (Box 11)
      - 1933 June 6 (Box 12)
  - Morgenthau, Henry (1891-1963)
    - 10 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
      - 1933 December 8 (Box 13)
      - 1934 March 10 (Box 13)
      - 1934 October 1 (2) (Box 15)